{
    "subject": "resource/Educating_Rita_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Michael_Caine",
    "human_readable": "The film Educating Rita stars Michael Caine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9422245025634766,
            "question": "Who starred in the film Educating Rita?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7492063045501709,
            "question": "Would you recommend the film Educating Rita?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7252916693687439,
            "question": "What might be the plot of a film called 'Educating Rita'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.707745373249054,
            "question": "What other actors have starred in films similar to Educating Rita?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6830043792724609,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that stars Michael Caine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6757990121841431,
            "question": "What genre is the film Educating Rita likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5781539678573608,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about the film Educating Rita?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43961599469184875,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a famous role Michael Caine played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40205174684524536,
            "question": "Are there any other films starring Michael Caine that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13201014697551727,
            "question": "Has Michael Caine won any awards for his acting?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Educating Rita stars Michael Caine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2735_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other films starring Michael Caine that you know of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2735_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a famous role Michael Caine played?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2735_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about the film Educating Rita?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2735_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2735_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the film \"Educating Rita\" and its cast, including a mention of Michael Caine playing the role of Frank, an Open University English Literature tutor. Therefore, the triple \"The film Educating Rita stars Michael Caine\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the film \"Educating Rita\" starred Michael Caine, which supports the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}